nylon.com 2019-12-21

# NYLON

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 23rd January 2019.

Maintaining your privacy and protecting your personal information is of the utmost importance to us. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) tells you about the information Nylon Media Inc. (“Nylon”, “We”, “Us” or “Our”) collects on this website, [www.nylon.com](https://www.nylon.com/) (the “Site”), and how we use that information. 

By accessing or using the Site you consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. If you do not agree with the Privacy Policy you should not access the Site and we would ask that you please stop using the Site immediately. 

Please also review our [Terms of Use](https://newnylon.rebelmouse.com/st/Legal_Page#terms-of-use) , which, together with this Privacy Policy and our [Intellectual Property](https://newnylon.rebelmouse.com/st/Legal_Page#intellectual-property) guidelines, constitutes our agreement with you regarding this Site. We recommend that you print or keep a digital copy of this Privacy Policy for future reference. 

A. Changes to the Privacy Policy

We may change, modify, or amend any provisions of the Privacy Policy from time to time. Any such changes or modifications will be effective immediately upon posting of the revisions on the Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of such changes or modifications constitutes your acceptance thereof. 

B. Users Over Thirteen (13)

We do not knowingly allow anyone under thirteen (13) to provide any personally identifying information to us without the express permission of a parent or guardian. If you are under thirteen (13), please do not provide us with any personally identifying information, such as your name, email address, or telephone number, unless you obtain the permission of your parent or guardian beforehand. We have no intention of collecting any personal information from individuals below the age of thirteen (13) without informed parental or guardian consent. We will delete any personal information collected that we later determine to be from an individual younger than the age of thirteen (13). 

C. External Links Disclaimer

The Site contains links to third party websites. If you choose to visit these other websites, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those other websites, and it is your responsibility to review the privacy policies of those websites to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies. 

D. Types of Information We Collect

We may collect two categories of information from you: (a) information you provide to us when you fill out forms on the Site, and (b) information collected by us as you navigate through the Site, which may include the model, setting, and specifications of the device you use to access the Site, date and/or time stamps, IP addresses, pages visited, content and ads viewed, the site you arrived from, and other clickstream data. 

E. Personally Identifying Information

We may include forms on the Site that ask you to provide your name, email address, and other contact information. You are not required to provide this information to gain access to and use the Site. We may also acquire your IP address, and user and/or device ID, which under certain jurisdictions is considered to be personally identifying information because it could be used to identify an individual or device when combined with other identifying information. 

F. Web Browser and Device Information and Anonymous Data

Similar to most other websites, we gather certain information on the Site and automatically store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (“IP”) addresses, smart phone and table MAC addresses, browser type, internet service provider (“ISP”), referring and exit pages, operating system, date and time stamps, and clickstream data. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track movement on the Site, and gather information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected information to personal information and will only be used in an anonymous way, sometimes aggregated with other data about other Site users. 

Your computer IP address, device MAC address, or other, similar addresses are logged with each visit and each action performed on the Site. This information is never provided to third parties, except as may be otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, and is logged only for a temporary period of time. 

G. Site Hosting

The Site is hosted by RebelMouse (“RebelMouse”). All information gathered on the Site is stored through RebelMouse’s data storage and databases. They store your information on a secure server behind a firewall. To learn more about how RebelMouse operates and stores information, please read RebelMouse’s [privacy policy](https://www.rebelmouse.com/st/Privacy_Policy). 

H. How Your Information May Be Used By Us

We use information about you to provide you with the services that you request from us, to respond to your questions and comments, and to measure interest in and improve our products and services and the Site. We may also use your contact information to inform you of any changes to Nylon or new features to the Site or to send you additional information about Nylon. We reserve the right to merge or co-mingle anonymous, non-personally identifiable information about you, your offline and online behavior, and/or the device you use to access the Site, with your personally identifying information for any lawful business purpose. 

Sharing with Third Parties: We do not share personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If our practices change, we will provide you with the relevant information as required by applicable law. 

Employees, Third-Party Processors and Third-Party Service Providers: We may disclose personal information to our employees, contractors, affiliates, distributors, dealers, vendors, and suppliers who process personal information on our behalf, or assist us in the provision or operation of the Site. 

Anonymous Information: We use anonymous information to analyze traffic on the Site, but we do not examine this information for individually identifying information. In addition, we may use anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis. 

Sharing or Disclosure of Personal Information: We may share with, or disclose to third parties personal information to provide you with our services, such as technical maintenance and advertising functionality, but solely to the extent required to provide those services; or in connection with a corporate transaction such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy. We may also disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Nylon, (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Nylon or the users of the Site, or (3) act under circumstances to protect the safety of the public or users of the Site. 

Employment Opportunities. If you provide your personally identifying information to us in connection with an employment inquiry, we may use such information to evaluate your job application, and for associated recruiting, reporting, and recordkeeping purposes. Way may maintain your information on file, regardless of whether you are hired. 

I. Use of Cookies, Storage, and Tracking Technologies

The Site and some of our third party service providers use cookies so you can get the most out of the Site. Cookies are small amounts of information in the form of text files that are stored on the device(s) you use to access the Site. Cookies allow us to monitor your use of the software and simplify your use of the Site. 

If you do not wish for cookies to be installed on the device(s) you use to access the Site, you can change the settings on your web browser or device to reject cookies. For more information about how to reject cookies using your web browser, please consult the “Help” section of your web browser. Please note that if you do set your web browser to reject cookies, you may not be able to access all of the features of the Site. 

We may at times place or store code or other types of information on the device or browser you use to access the Site, or in our emails or other communications to you. This may include cookies, locally shared objects, and HTML5. Additionally, we will occasionally use web beacons, web bugs, internet or pixel tags, digital fingerprinting, and other tracking technologies on the Site and in our communications with you. Both Nylon and our third party service providers may use these technologies in relation to the Site for any lawful business purpose. This may include, without limitation, tracking the movement of users through the Site, to help diagnose problems with our servers, to gather broad demographic information, to record registration and personalized information, and to otherwise administer and operate the Site. 

Additionally, the Site contains content and links to other websites that are operated by third parties that may also use cookies. We do not control these third party sites or cookies, and this Privacy Policy does not apply to them. Please consult the privacy policies of those third party websites, many of which are linked below, to find out how they collect and use your information, and to establish whether and for what purpose they use cookies and/or Local Device Storage. 

J. Third Party Service Providers and Information Processing

We also use various third party services providers, some of whom may process personally identifying information. We use these third party services providers to offer you the best possible experience when using the Site. Please note that we have no control over how any cookies or other tools used by these third party service providers. You can learn more about these third party service providers and how they may use information by following the links to their respective privacy policies, below. 

We use Google Analytics, a web-based analytic services provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). This service places cookies on your computer to help analyze how you and other users use the Site. The information generated by the cookie containing information about your use of the Site will be transmitted and stored by Google on their servers. Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the Site, compile reports on website activity for us, as operators of the Site, and provide other services relating to Site activity. Google may transfer this information to third parties as required by law, or where such third parties process the information on their behalf. For more information on these services, please click [here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en). We also use Google Ads Manager, that allows us to customize display ads for people who previously visited the Site. To opt out of Google’s use of cookies, visit Google’s [Ads Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en#display_optout). 

We use the Conversion Tracking or Custom Audience Pixel service of Facebook Inc. (“Facebook”). The service allows us to follow the actions of users after they are redirected by clicking on a Facebook advertisement. As a result, we can record the efficacy of Facebook advertisements for statistical and market research purposes. The collected data are saved and processed by Facebook. Facebook is able to connect the data with your Facebook account and use the data for their own advertising purposes. For more information regarding Facebook Conversion Tracking, please visit Facebook’s [privacy policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/). To find instructions how to revoke permission for this service, please click [here](https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry_product=ad_settings_screen). 

Additionally, we use the following third party service providers to measure the performance and verify delivery of our advertisements to you, to provide insights on user behavior on the Site, and perform other functions to provide you with the best version of our Site. Please follow the links provided below to review any of our third party service provider’s privacy and information processing policies. 

Celtra: <https://www.celtra.com/privacy-policy/>

comScore: <https://www.comscore.com/About/Privacy-Policy>

Hotjar: <https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy>

JWPlayer: <https://www.jwplayer.com/privacy/>

Mailchimp: <https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/>

Mixpanel: <https://mixpanel.com/legal/privacy-policy/>

Moat: <https://moat.com/privacy>

OpenX: <https://www.openx.com/legal/privacy-policy/>

Outbrain : <https://www.outbrain.com/legal/privacy#privacy-policy>

Parsley: <https://www.parse.ly/privacy-policy/>

PubExchange: <https://www.pubexchange.com/legal/privacy>

Rubicon: <https://rubiconproject.com/privacy/>

Teads: <https://www.teads.tv/privacy-policy/>

Unruly: <https://unruly.co/privacy/>

K. Security

Nylon has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you. This includes: (a) ensuring the physical security of our offices; (b) ensuring the physical and digital security of our equipment and devices by using passwords and encryption; (c) maintaining a data protection policy for our employees; and (d) limiting access to personal information we collect solely to those who need to use it in the course of their work. As no data transmission is completely secure and no physical or electronic security is impenetrable, we cannot make any guarantees about our ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, to you or to any third party arising out of any loss, misuse, or alteration of your information and are not responsible for any loss of such information or the consequences thereof. 

In the event we learn that the security of any information provided to us or in our control may have been compromised, we may notify you of same. If notification is appropriate, we may notify you by e-mail, push notification, or other method. 

L. California Privacy Rights

California law requires that operators of websites and online services disclose how they respond to a Do Not Track signal and whether other third parties may collect personal information about an individual’s online activities from their website or service. Some browsers have incorporated “Do Not Track” features. Most of these features, when turned on, send a signal or preference to the website or online service that a user visits, indicating that the user does not wish to be tracked. Because there is not yet a common understanding of how to interpret Do Not Track signals, we do not currently respond to Do Not Track signals. We continue to work with the online industry to define a common understanding of how to treat Do Not Track signals. 

M. Visiting our Site from outside the United States

If you are visiting the Site from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be stored and processed in the United States, where our servers are located and operated. Please be aware that the data protection and other laws of the United States might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. However, please be assured that we take steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using the Site, you agree that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it, as described in this Privacy Policy. 

If you are a resident of the EEA or Switzerland, you are entitled to the following rights. Contact us per the contact information provided below to exercise these rights.  In order to verify your identity, we may require you to provide us with personal information prior to accessing any records containing personal information. 

Right to access and rectify your personal information: You have the right to obtain information about our processing of your personal information and a copy of your personal information that we store. You have the right to request that we update your information if it is inaccurate or incomplete. 

Right to request erasure of your personal information: You have the right to have your personal information erased from our systems if the personal information is no longer necessary for the purpose for which it was collected or you withdraw consent and no other legal basis for processing exists. 

Right to restrict our processing of your personal information: You have the right to restrict our processing if you contest the accuracy of the personal information we store about you, our processing is deemed unlawful and you oppose erasure of your personal information, or we no longer need the personal information for the purposes for which we collected it but we must store it to comply with our legal obligations. 

Right to portability of your personal information: You have the right to receive your personal information and to transmit it to another controller where our processing is based on consent you gave us and was carried out by automated means. 

Right to object to our processing of your personal information: You have the right to object to our processing where we process personal information based on legitimate interest. 

N. Contacting Us

In certain circumstances, you may have a right to access or object to the use of personal information held about you. You may also ask us to rectify, update, erase, restrict or to share your information in a usable format with another company, in each case subject to applicable law. We encourage you to contact us to update or correct your information. We will make every effort to comply with your request unless we have a lawful reason not to do so. 

The Site is operated by Nylon. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, our practices related to the Site, or any other inquiries please feel contact us at the following email address: [legal@nylon.com](mailto:legal@nylon.com).
